# **Dmitry Beskov**

#### Frontend developer

Tbilisi, Georgia | dmitry.beskov@outlook.com | besdar.github.io

## Summary

I'm a React front-end developer with over 4 years of experience. When I work, I usually point out the weaknesses in the company's processes and projects, and make suggestions to make our daily work more effective, fun and/or easier. I also try to fix code issues that I see on a regular basis. I really love what I do and I want to continue to grow in the frontend and create something great and special.

## Work experience

## *IettyCloud (UCaaS)* 2022 - 2024

### **Senior Software Developer**

- Was consistently scored 3 out of 5 as exceeding expectations in a performance review process, and received only positive feedbacks from my colleagues
- Worked simultaneously in more than 4 teams (about 30 people) with more than 3 projects
- Was the author of more than 50 technical tasks designed to improve the performance and quality of the code
- Was involved in the recruitment process and developed a technical interview knowledge base for all roles across the company, which improved our interview process
- Created an account generation Chrome extension tool for the company, which made the daily work of both QA engineers and developers much easier

In this role, I was usually responsible for the creation, updating and maintenance of various sub-modules for customer account pages and internal administration pages.

Stack: TS, React&Redux, Java&Kotlin, GraphQL

**Foxford (EdTech)** 2020 - 2022

## Frontend developer

- Implemented code review for the team, was an organizer of frontend meetings
- · Added large adjustment to the ESLint of a team project, added Stylelint, adjusted bundling and CI of the project
- Optimized JS code of the project and work process of the team developers now are writing faster and more stable code

Practically was a team leader, worked a lot with HTML&CSS and performed managerial activities like teamwork process optimization on various development stages

Stack: JS&FlowType, JQuery, HTML&CSS, React&Effector, NodeJS

## **BIOS (B2B, startup)** 2019 - 2020

### Software developer

- Web-development: React and Redux / PHP / Typescript / 1C-Bitrix. Maintenence, project development. Self-education, selfrefactoring
- System administration: Configuring and deployment of (web-) servers and platforms (1C and others), OS errors resolving, project's git trees management
- · Made Telegram client and TOTP algorithm two-factor authentication development for 1C platform

Was assigned and successfully resolved the most responsible and fundamental tasks, strictly followed the prescribed project timing, found solutions for various business tasks, independently set personal goals for further business improvement

Stack: React&Redux, HTML&CSS, JS, PHP, HTTP, NodeJS, 1C

#### Education

Saint Petersburg State Electrotechnical University 2014 - 2018

«Communication Technologies and Communication Systems»

**Faculty of Radio Engineering and Telecommunications**